nochex.com 2013-05-28

# Privacy

## Data Protection

Any information you provide us with will only be disclosed in accordance with the Data Protection Act of 1998.

## Required Information

To open a Nochex account you must tell us certain personal information such as your name, email address, date of birth and postal address. Depending on the type of account you may also be asked to supply additional information such as the nature of your business, web address and business address.  For security, you must also submit a password and answer security questions. 

For certain transactions you need to provide financial information such as your debit card details. We only collect the information that is required by regulation and law for us to process your transactions securely and protect you against fraud.

## Use of Personal Information

We only use your personal information to service your account and to improve our service to you. As part of our normal business operation, we do share some financial information with banks, card processing and verification services. 

Unless required by law, these organisations may not use your information for secondary purposes. Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law when we believe that such action is necessary to comply with current judicial proceedings, a court order or legal process serviced on our web site. Otherwise, under no circumstances will information you provide to Nochex be transmitted in any way to a third party without your consent.

##  Cookies 

We may collect aggregated statistical information for purposes of improving our service and your experience with Nochex. This data does not contain personally identifying information, such as your name or email address.

Nochex uses cookies. A cookie is a small text file that can be stored on your computer's hard drive. It may be stored and updated at various times as you access the website. Each time you visit the website, the server may deliver certain customised information to your computer based on the data stored in your cookie. 

This allows Nochex to tailor the service to your preferences. You are not obliged to accept a cookie and you may modify your browser so that it will not accept cookies. If you do not want to accept cookies please use the help tools provided with your internet browser to find out how to achieve this.

We never use cookies to retrieve information from your computer which was not originally contained in the cookie. We use cookies and IP addresses for system administration and to monitor aggregate non-personalised information (such as anonymous statistics related to the take up or use of services, or to patterns of browsing). 

Certain non-personal information about users is recorded by the standard operation of Nochex's internet servers. Examples of this type of information include the type of browsers being used, its operating system and the domain names (not e-mail addresses) of users. 

Because we use privacy neutral cookies we do not seek to obtain consent from users for any cookies used on our website. 

## Links

This web site contains links to other websites, however Nochex is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these external websites. We recommend you, our users, to be aware that when you leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

## Changing information

You can update your account information in the personal details section of the Nochex web site. However, we cannot delete user information because of legal, regulatory and technical back up requirements.
